Hello. I'm Dr.
Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon:)And welcome to Sheldon Cooper
Presents: Fun with Flags,
(Sheldon:)the Final Episode
Flagtacular.
(gasps)
(Sheldon:)I knew it was coming.
Still scary.
(Sheldon:)Now, I'm sure you're thinking,
"The final episode?
(Sheldon:)Who will stand between
us and flag ignorance?"
(Amy:)I know I was thinking that.
(Amy:)Is this a show on flags
or mind reading?
(Sheldon:)But the truth is I can no longer
balance a full-time career,
(Sheldon:)a popular Internet show,
and a girlfriend.
(Amy:)And he really does have one,
you jerks on the comment board.
(Sheldon:)So as they say, all good
things must come to an end.
(Amy:)After only 232 episodes.
(Sheldon:)233 if we
include the one
(Sheldon:)somebody forgot
to press record on.
(quietly): You said
you weren't gonna bring that up.
(quietly): And you
said you pressed record.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, please
sit back, relax,
(Sheldon:)and join us as we
take our final lap...
(Sheldon:)...as indicated by the
waving of this racing flag.
(Sheldon:)And, of course, white flags
can also represent surrender,
(Sheldon:)the Stewards of Gondor, and
the Japanese Minamoto clan,
(Sheldon:)but I'm sure you remember
that from episode 62,
"White Flags: Who's
Wavin' 'Em and Why?"
(Amy:)That was a good one.
(Sheldon:)It was so good.